wlci.in 2015-04-23

# Fashion & Graphic Designing Training Institute| Business Management Courses & Programs â€“ WLCI College

##  Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the [ products, services and websites](http://www.wlci.in/contactus.html) offered by WLCI College India. Sometimes, we may post product specific privacy notices or Help Center materials to explain our products in more detail. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to [ contact](http://www.wlci.in/contactus.html) us through our website or write to us at 

##  Information we collect and how we use it for our WLCI College, India.

###  Website Detail :

Entire content of the website has been gathered to the best of our knowledge and belief, and the company endeavors to keep it up to date. In particular, we reserve the entire right to update and/or modify and/or remove this data anytime and without any prior notice. Please note that the company holds no responsibility for incorrect or no longer correct statements, quotes or descriptions and thereby excludes liability for any losses resulting from such wrong information. 

Further, the company has every right to bring about legal action on students who misuse/alter/reproduce the content/ information available on the website 

###  Data Privacy Policy

Our data privacy policy strictly conforms to the international legal regulations set down in accordance to the protection of data collected from people visiting our website. WLCI College, India treats all personal data obtained via internet and our website carefully and confidentially so that no physical/mental harm is instilled up on the person, with regard to the collected data . Personal data that has possibly been known to us will be kept secret, privacy will be respected and information will be used exclusively for the purpose for which it was made known to us. Without seeking approval of the respective person, this data will neither be made accessible to third parties, nor transferred to them in any form or manner.

###  Changes to our Privacy Policy

WLCI College, India reserves the entire right to modify/amend/remove this privacy statement anytime and without any reason. Nothing contained herein creates or is intended to create a contract/agreement between WLCI College, India and any user visiting the WLCI College, India website or providing identifying information of any kind.

###  DND Policy 

If you wish to stop any further sms/email alerts/contacts from our side, all you need to do is to send an email at [ mail@wlci.in ](mailto:mail@wlci.in) with your mobile numbers and you will be excluded from the alerts list. 

###  Contact Details:

Email :[mail@wlci.in](mailto:mail@wlci.in)
